<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ember on Blog de Carlo Gilmar</title>
    <link>https://carlogilmar.github.io/tags/ember/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ember on Blog de Carlo Gilmar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://carlogilmar.github.io/tags/ember/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ember 2018 Roadmap: A call for blog post</title>
      <link>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/ember-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/ember-call/</guid>
      <description>This blog post is a response to Ember’s 2018 Roadmap: A Call for Blog Posts Last November 2017 I had to build an application for make exams to evaluate teachers from a popular university. In the beginning this project was considered only for one person (me), so we decide learn Ember JS for this project.
The Beginning My previous experiences making front-end projects was using simple javascript and coffee script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ember JS First Steps</title>
      <link>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/ember-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/ember-first/</guid>
      <description>In the last post Learning Ember I talk about how to start with Ember.
Now, after nights studying Ember I think that learning this framework is difficult because it require think first in Ember Concepts.
After nights studying Ember I can say that learning this framework is difficult because you have to think first in their main concepts, and if you have some experience with other frameworks or transpilers ( coffee script, typescript, elm) probably you will be confused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PacktPub Review: Effective Jenkins</title>
      <link>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/effectivejenkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/effectivejenkins/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I reviewed a video course from Packt Publishing: “Effective Jenkins: Improving Quality in the Delivery Pipeline with Jenkins”
 Thanks to Packt Publishing for this opportunity, and thanks to Dwayne D&amp;rsquo;Souza for the collaboration!  So, I want to talk about the content of this course.
Before to Start This course is for people who know the basics about Jenkins. If you don’t, I would recommend learning about this from their previous courses:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Ember JS</title>
      <link>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/learning-ember/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/learning-ember/</guid>
      <description>Follow with learning more about Ember Js as our JS framework, I have to talk about my learning experience.
When I was searching about Ember I found a lot of resources: posts, books, videos, courses and more. Everything looks good, until I had to start my first projects.
Before to start  I think that is good to know the context about it. Ember JS was born as a fork from SproutCore Framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Ember Js</title>
      <link>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/emberjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 09:13:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/emberjs/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post in this year.
Recently we have to develop a project about teacher training for a private university in Mexico City.
There are a lot of javascript frameworks and transpilers: Angular JS, Vue JS, Meteor, Aurelia JS, React JS, Ionic JS, Typescript, CoffeeScript, Elm, etc. We decided learn and use Ember JS for develop our frontend, and Spring/Groovy for the backend.
About Ember Js  Ember is a JavaScript front-end framework designed to help you build websites with rich and complex user interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>