<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Swift on Blog de Carlo Gilmar</title>
    <link>https://carlogilmar.github.io/categories/swift/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Swift on Blog de Carlo Gilmar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://carlogilmar.github.io/categories/swift/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Swift</title>
      <link>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/learning-swift/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/learning-swift/</guid>
      <description>Learning Swift Recently I have been studying about Swift. I think that the learning experience is a wonderful resource for other persons who are in the same situation, so I consider valuable talk about this. First Steps When I start to learn swift I decide to watch videos and demonstrations about how to use the Xcode for build iOS apps, but, for be honest, I couldn’t understand some things: optionals, constrains, auto layout… This was my first experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fibonacci Sequence Review with Swift</title>
      <link>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/fibonacci/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 09:13:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/fibonacci/</guid>
      <description>Fibonacci Sequence With Swift 4.0 One of the firsts examples is the Fibonacci Sequence, although It’s a common programming problem, also It’s a curious problem for be solve with swift.
This is a sequence of numbers, which start in the third element as the sum of the previous two numbers. The next number is the sum of the previous two numbers too.
 0, 1, (0+1), (1 + (0+1))</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First iOS App: Sending Messages to Slack</title>
      <link>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/first-ios-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 00:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carlogilmar.github.io/post/first-ios-app/</guid>
      <description>Hey! I have been learning how to program swift because I want to write iOS apps.
For the first, I considered start with recognize my previous concepts in this new language for me, here is my &amp;ldquo;fizzbuzz&amp;rdquo; example:
 My guide to learn Swift and iOS are the follow videos and books:
 Swift Mastering The Core Concepts Building iOS 10 Applications with Swift iOS Programming The Big Nerd Ranch Guide 6Th Edition  My First App First, I need to understand this:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>